holaquiz.com 2019-04-01

# How much do your friends know you? Create your HolaQuiz!

#### Privacy Policy

This privacy policy is encapsulated to make users aware of their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) that can be used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. In order to understand how our website uses your Personally Identifiable Information, please read our privacy policy carefully. It will help you to have a clear picture of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your PII.

Personal information collected by us, from the people that visit our website is stated as follows:

  1. We collect information from you while you play the quiz game, register on our site or fill out a form. When playing on our site, as obvious it is, you may be asked to enter your: name and select your region or choose language. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

  2. Double Dart Cookie: Google is a third party vendor who uses cookies to serve ads on our website. Google uses the DART cookie which helps in serving ads based on your visits to various sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the use of the DART cookie when you go to the Google ad and content network privacy policy here - [https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads](https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads).

  3. Use of Facebook social plugins & Facebook Re / Marketing Features

  * We use facebook social plugins to enhance our services. The plugins are usually recognizable by one of the Facebook logos (eg "f" on a blue tile or a "thumbs up" sign)

  * Within our online offer are "Facebook pixels" and "App Analytics" functions (collectively referred to as "Facebook Re / Marketing Features") of the social network Facebook. With these functions, Facebook is able to target our visitors for the presentation of advertisements, so-called "Facebook Ads". Accordingly, we use Facebook Re / Marketing features to display the Facebook Ads we submit only to Facebook users as well as those Facebook users who might be interested in similar features (so-called "Lookalike Audiences"). This helps in keeping the Facebook Ads in line with the potential interest of users and are not annoying. We can also track the effectiveness of Facebook ads for statistical and market research purposes by seeing if users have been redirected to our site after clicking on a Facebook ad.

  * The data collected about you are anonymous to us, so do not give us any conclusions about the identity of the users. However, the data is stored and processed by Facebook, so that a connection to the respective user profile is possible. The processing of the data by Facebook is part of Facebook's data usage policy. For further information on the functioning of Facebook's Data Use Policy, use the link: [https://www.facebook.com/policy.php](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php).

  * You may object and disable these functions by following the instructions on the usage-based advertising settings: https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads or the contradiction on the page http://www.aboutads.info / choices or the EU side http://www.youronlinechoices.com explain. The settings are platform-independent, ie they are adopted for all devices, such as desktop computers or mobile devices.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you or enter information on our site while starting a Quiz.

**How do we use your information?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  1. Your information helps us to personalize your experience better.

  2. We constantly strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback you give to us.

  3. Your information helps us in improving the customer service and requests. 

  4. We may send periodic emails regarding inquiries, and/or other requests or questions to the email address you provide to us in future.

**How do we protect your information?**

A variety of security measures are performed to maintain the safety of your personal information. We only provide simple playful quizzes. Our website never asks for credit card numbers. Neither does our site uses Malware Scanning.

Your personal information (if any) is kept confidential and secured by safe networks and is only accessible to very few people who have exclusive access rights to such systems.

**Are 'cookies' used by us?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We only use cookies to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to better site experiences and tools in the future by compiling aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction.

You can choose to turn off all cookies; also you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is sent. In order to do this go to your browser settings and look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

**What if you disable cookies in your browser:**

If a user disables the cookies, Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not be availed to you. 

**Third-party disclosure**

We assure you that we do not trade, sell, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.

**Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may at sometimes offer third-party products or services on our website. All the third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. Therefore our website holds no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we welcome any feedback about these sites to protect the integrity of our website.

**We have implemented the following:**

Along with third-party vendors such as Google, our website uses first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers. All this is together to compile data regarding user interactions along with some ad impressions as well as other ad service functions because they relate to our website.

Upon creation of this privacy policy, a link will be added on our homepage or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website. Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can easily be found on the page specified above.

**Any changes will be notified to you at : **

  * Our Privacy Policy Page

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

The privacy policy stated above applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**The users can change their personal information:**

  * By chatting with us or by sending us a support ticket within 1 business day.

**Contact Us**

For any further questions and queries regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us on contactholaquiz@gmail.com
